Such a big and dangerous snake came to our
house today that seeing it would make one cry.  At
6:00 in the morning, Mast was lost in his snake dreams.
But who knew she would
come home to take revenge?  When I looked down, I was stunned.
She is
sitting here happily as if it is her father
's house.  I asked my sister where did you come from?
So the sister told that I was sweeping.   As
soon as I removed the wardrobe for cleaning, I
saw a snake.  Brother,
look at Reena, how shocked she is after seeing this.
Well, we called Snake Race and
brother came running in the morning itself.  He looked at him and
asked how did he enter your house.  I
said the story is very big.
Take it away from here quickly.  My poor sister stands there in shock.
Brother quickly
wore gloves on his hands, picked up his weapon and with
respect and honour took away Nagrani ji who had occupied our house
and
showed her the way out.  This is really great
brother.  I saw how they were running to save themselves.
We said we have come to save, not to kill.